<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Sinal's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://meassinal.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://meassinal.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-09-04T16:39:38+07:00</updated>
  <id>http://meassinal.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Meas Sinal]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaving Yoolk Inc to Start a Journey]]></title>
    <link href="http://meassinal.github.io/blog/2015/09/04/leaving-yoolk-inc-to-start-a-journey/"/>
    <updated>2015-09-04T15:51:50+07:00</updated>
    <id>http://meassinal.github.io/blog/2015/09/04/leaving-yoolk-inc-to-start-a-journey</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yoolk Inc is a great company where I have been working as a software developer for about six years. It is truly an exciting and enjoyable working place. Yoolk Inc provides opportunities for its software developers to use latest open source technologies, modern technologies, and best practises used by software developers around the world. Moreover, People are very nice, helpful and talented that I learned a lot from; and I feel that I have been surrounded with  the best. So I can say Yoolk Inc is one of the best software companies in Phnom Penh, Cambodia  you ever find.</p>

<p>However today 4th September 2015 is my last working day. It is quite tough to make a decision to leave such a great company. But time goes by and life can’t stay still. Life has changed! I want to go on more adventures to pursue my dreams, passions, opportunities, leadership, and entrepreneurship. I will definitely start something that really matters.</p>

<p>Finally I would like to thank everybody in the whole company for your kindness, cooperation and knowledge sharing. Without all of you around me, I would never ever have been like today.  After my leaving I wish the company will get great success and grow bigger and bigger in the future.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
